(マダラ)よし。
Good…
(我愛羅)ナルト！
Naruto!
(扉間)やめろ マダラ。
Stop, Madara!
(マダラ)言ったはずだ。
残された時間は 少ないとな。
I already told you
that you had little time left.
Obito…
(ミナト)オビト… 輪廻眼を
マダラの手に渡すまいと→
He's reluctant to give up
the Rinnegan to Madara…
抵抗しているんだ。
You stubborn fool…
You're almost dead anyway!
(ゼツ)しつこいな。
死にかけのくせに。
(サクラ)しっかりして！
負けないで！
Hang in there! Don't give up!
アンタは 強い。 必ず 必ず助かる！
You're strong! You'll pull through!
《私のチャクラが もう…》
My chakra's almost all…
Sasuke's not good, he's really gonna…
(香燐)サスケが本当に… 本当に！
このままじゃ
このままじゃ ナルトが…。
At this rate, Naruto's going to…
(サクラ/香燐)死んで…。
– die!
On the Brink of Death
The Nine Tails' chakra…
《九尾のチャクラが…》
《はっ… 心音も聞こえない》
No heartbeat or pulse...
そんな！
しっかりしろ ナルト！
No way!
Hang in there, Naruto!
なんで!?
医療忍術が効かない！
What's going on?!
My Medical Ninjutsu isn't
working on him!
九尾を抜かれてしまって
いるからだろう。
It's probably because the Nine Tails
has been extracted from him!
まさか！
That's impossible!
マダラにやられた。
Madara got him.
But there's a way to save him!
だが 助かる手はある。
だから こうして急いでいるのだ。
That's why we're hurrying!
(サクラ)どこへ!?
四代目火影のところへだ。
To where?!
To where the Fourth Hokage is.
((九喇嘛 : 風影のガキ！
頼みがある！
Hey, kid! Kazekage! Do me a favor!
ソイツの父
四代目火影 ミナトの体の中に→
His father…
One-half of me is sealed inside
the Fourth Hokage, Minato.
わしの半身が封印されている。
ソイツを わしの代わりとして入れろ。
So transplant that other half
into Naruto. That will save him.
それで ナルトは助かる。
(九喇嘛)四代目のところへ急げ！
Hurry to the Fourth Hokage!
He has the Teleportation Jutsu.
ヤツには瞬身の術がある。
どうにか連絡をして
向こうから…。
Can't we just contact him over there
somehow and have him come here?
That won't work!
それは無理だ。
ヤツの瞬身の術は→
His Teleportation Jutsu is written
into my Sealing Formula.
わしの封印式に
書き込まれたもの。
わしが抜かれた時点で
それは消え… ううっ。
Once I'm extracted,
it will disappear…
とにかく四代目火影の
ところへ連れていけ！
Just rush Naruto over
to the Fourth Hokage.
わかったな 我愛羅！
Got that, Gaara?!
Kid Kazekage…
I'm counting on you!
(頼んだぞ 風影のガキ))
それが九尾に言われたことだ。
That's what Nine Tails told me.
今のところ それ以外に
ナルトが助かる方法はない。
Right now, there's no other way
to save Naruto!
そこまで あと どのくらい？
How much longer 'til
we get there?
Several kilometers!
まだ 数キロある。
I'll do whatever it takes
with what little chakra I have left!
《サクラ : 残り少ないチャクラで
できること！》
よし！
All right!
この私がみるかぎり
簡単には死なせやしないわ！
As long as I'm here,
I am not going to let you die!
とばすぞ！
うん！
I'm going to go at full speed!
Right!
クッ…。
せめて わしの禁術で
魂だけでも…。
If I could just…save his soul
with my Forbidden Jutsu…
I can't sense any chakra
in him anymore.
もう チャクラが感知できぬ。
瞬身どころか 体が動かぬ。
I can't even move my body…
let alone use Teleportation.
マダラめ…。
Damn you, Madara!
うわぁ!!
(水月)え!? 香燐のヤツ
飛び出してっちゃったよ！
Karin just went charging ahead!
(大蛇丸)香燐を援護するわよ。
Let's go back up Karin!
ゲッ 敵の隙を突くとか
何か作戦が…。
Shouldn't we wait for an opening,
or have some sort of plan?
Whoa, you're not getting past me.
おっと ここは通さないよ。
No one's answered my question yet.
まだ 僕の質問に
誰も答えてないだろう！
うちの邪魔すんな!!
Don't get in my way!
サスケのところへ行くんだ！
どけ この野郎！
I'm going to Sasuke!
Move, you bastard!
You've got to be kidding!
Karin is amazing.
ウソ… すげえな 香燐。
(重吾)これは…。
What is this?!
(大蛇丸)うずまきクシナと同じ力。
The same power as
Kushina Uzumaki's.
After all this time,
she's finally attained it…
《今になって やっと…》
Oh no…
あらら せっかくのオモチャ
壊してくれちゃって！
You just broke my little toy!
うちをなめるな！
Do not…underestimate me!
フッ… ２丁！
Double Blast!
やるね。
Not bad.
I can't move…
動けな…。
《呪印か》
A Curse Mark!
ハッハ！ 残念でした！
Too bad!
A-Amazing…
す… すげえ。
(ヒルゼン)大蛇丸のヤツ 抜けおったか。
Orochimaru…They got past it!
まいっか。
It's no big deal.
It's too late even if
you go over there anyway.
向こうへ行っても
もう遅いからね。
だけど お前たちは
やっつけちゃうよ。
But as for you guys…
I'm going to take you down.
感心している場合ではない。
わしらも行くぞ！
Stop your ogling!
We must go too.
《にしても あやつ 何者じゃ？》
Still…who is he?
(重吾)大丈夫か？ 香燐。
Are you all right, Karin?
ああ… んなことより…。
Yeah… But never mind me.
サスケが…
サスケが感知できねえんだよ！
Sasuke! I can't sense Sasuke!
これが 六道の力か。
So this is Six Paths power…
あとは 左目だな。
Now, for that left eye.
((ナルト : いずれ火影の名を名乗る
超エリート忍者！
I'm a super elite ninja who's gonna
be the Hokage someday…
(うずまきナルトという。 覚えとけ！))
Remember my name…
Naruto Uzumaki!
((俺ってば 火影になって→
I'm gonna become the Hokage!
(どの先代も
超えてやるんだってばよ！))
The Hokage that surpasses all
previous Hokage, ya know!
《かつての アンタのバカげた夢は
今は もう…》
That silly dream you once had…
no longer seems silly.
《逝かせない。
逝かせて たまるか！
I will not let you die!
絶対に
死なせるわけにはいかないのよ！
You're not going to die,
no matter what!
アンタの夢は…
今は もう 目の前なんだから!!》
Your dream…
is right before your eyes now!
あ… 誰だ？
Who's there?!
Depending on the situation,
《大蛇丸は
サスケの状態によっては→
Orochimaru might try
to steal Sasuke's body.
体を奪いにかかるかもしれない。
それが君麻呂の想いでもあるが→
It's what Kimimaro had wanted,
but I doubt Karin would allow it.
香燐は
それを許しはしないだろう》
あっ！
サスケのいた場所に誰かいる！
There's someone else
where Sasuke is.
チャクラに覚えは？
Do you recognize the chakra?
ない！ けど…。
No! But…
けど 何？
But what?
このチャクラ…
すごくイヤな感じがする。
This chakra…
has a real nasty feel to it!
なら もっと急がないとね。
Then we need to hurry even more.
どこの馬の骨かもしれない輩に→
We don't know what this stranger
might do to Sasuke.
サスケ君が何されるか
わからないものね。
《彼の風は ここまでかしらね》
Is this the end for him?
《チクショウ！》
Damn it…
うわっ！
Yikes!
Karin! If you up the pace too much,
you're going to collapse soon.
(大蛇丸)香燐！ だからって
そんなにとばすと→
すぐバテるわよ！
(ガイ)青春パワー マックスで
みんなのところへ行くぞ！
Let's head to the others
with youth power to the max!
リー！ テンテン！
Lee! Tenten!
Yes, sir! But you're falling over,
Guy Sensei!
(リー)はい！
ですが バッテバッテです ガイ先生！
(テンテン)心に体が
まったくついてってないじゃん。
Your body isn't keeping up
with your spirit!
あっ！
あれは 我愛羅君の砂。
サクラさんもいたような気が…。
That's Gaara's sand…
I think I saw Sakura too…
(テンテン)なんで
引き返してんだろう？
Why are they retreating?
カカシは まだ
俺たちを追い抜いてはいないな。
Kakashi hasn't overtaken
and passed us yet, has he?
うん。
ナルトにもらった九尾のチャクラが消え→
No.
The Nine Tails' chakra we got
from Naruto has disappeared.
医療班である
サクラが移動しているとなると→
And Sakura, a Medical Ninja,
is on the move…
どうも カカシのほうで
何か起こりかけている気がする。
I have a feeling something
is going down on Kakashi's side.
引き返すぞ リー テンテン！
We're heading back, Lee! Tenten!
俺の熱い血が騒ぐのだ。
My red-hot blood is boiling!
It must be a super premonition!
スーパー胸騒ぎですね。
え～っ！
Nothing good can come out of
being stuck with
この熱血ド天然野郎どもと
一緒にいても→
this hot-blooded, airhead duo!
ロクなことないよ。
ネジよ なぜ私を１人にしたのよ。
Neji, why did you leave me?
はいはい 引き返しましょう。
Okay, let's head back.
引き返せばいいんですね。
引き返しますとも…。
You want to go back, right?
Fine, let's do that.
《ネジ ホントに許さないんだから》
Neji…
I'm never going to forgive you.
《待ってろよ
すぐに駆けつけてやる カカシ》
Wait for me! I'll be there
as fast as I can, Kakashi.
(オビト)カカシ 早く左目を…。
Hurry, Kakashi…the left eye.
(カカシ)
オビトの意識がしっかりしている。
Obito's conscience is clear.
Now's our chance.
今がチャンスですね。
The problem is how to tear
Obito away from that guy.
あとは オビトからアイツを
どう引きはがすかが問題だよ。
左目を敵の
手に渡すわけにもいかないしね。
And we can't hand over
that left eye to the enemy…
少しばかり体が重いな。
何かが胸でつかえてやがる。
I feel a little heavy.
There's something catching
in my chest.
六道の忍具か フン くだらん。
The Sage of
Six Paths' Ninja Tools, eh?
Useless.
But now I'm lighter.
《だが 軽くはなった》
私たちが今更 戻って
どうにかなるんですか？
What will we accomplish
by returning now?
テンテン ぶつくさ言うな。
Tenten, don't grumble!
何やら 得体の知れない恐怖が→
I just have this gut feeling that
some unknown horror is approaching.
近づいてきている気がするのだ。
はい。
Yes, sir.
(３人)ぐぁ～！
２人とも大丈夫？
Are you two all right?!
は はい…。
うっ…。
Yes…!
えっ ウソ!? これって 確か…。
No way…
These are definitely the—!
お前らも しつこいな。
You guys are stubborn too!
もう オビトの意識が
はっきりしてない。
Obito's consciousness is
no longer stable.
カカシ 行くよ。
Let's go, Kakashi.
待て ミナト。
Hold on, Minato!
チャクラを感知仕様に変えてみろ。
Switch your chakra to Sensory Mode!
ま… まさか!?
No way!
こっちに気をとられすぎたな。
We were distracted by
what was happening here.
間違いなく
わしの半身は抜かれちまってる。
There's no mistake.
My other half has
already been extracted!
先生…。
Sensei?
カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei!
何があった？
What happened?
ナルトの中の九尾が抜き取られて。
The Nine Tails was extracted
from Naruto!
このままじゃ…。
At this rate he'll—!
ナルト…。
Naruto…
ナルトの九尾からの伝言だ。
Fourth Hokage, I bring a message
from Naruto's Nine Tails!
四代目火影。
アンタの中の九尾の半身を→
He said to transplant
the other half of Nine Tails
ナルトの中へ入れてやれと。
that you have within you,
into Naruto!
それでナルトは助かると…。
That will save him!
ほう…。
Oh…
カカシ ヤツを頼む。
わかりました。
Kakashi, he's yours.
I understand.
俺もだ。
I'll help!
((じゃあ 行ってくる。
(クシナ)気をつけて。
I'm going.
Be careful.
ああ。 子供の顔を見るまでは
絶対に死ねないよ。
Of course! I'm not dying
until I see my child's face.
この子が生まれたら→
Once this baby is born…
心配事が２つになるわね。
I'll have two things
to worry about.
大丈夫。
Don't worry!
この子は俺が守るよ。
I'll protect the kid!
どんなことがあっても
どんな手を使っても。
No matter what happens,
and no matter what it takes!
でも あなたは火影で忙しいし→
But you're busy being Hokage,
この子は やんちゃで
火影になりたいって→
and I get the feeling he's going to
be mischievous and unreasonable
ムチャばかりして
きかないと思うし…。
and say he wants to be the Hokage…
(クシナ)女心にも鈍感で…。
(ミナト)ちょっ ちょっと待って！
– He'll be clueless about girls…
– Hey, wait!
先生に刃向かって そして…。
待って！
– And he'll defy his teachers! And…
– Hold on!
もう 生まれる前から
心配してるし…。
The child's not even born yet…
You're worrying too much!
心配しすぎだよ。
なんで この子が男の子で→
Besides, how do you
know it's a boy?
しかも火影になりたいだなんて
生まれてもないのに わかるの？
Or that he'll want to be
the Hokage even before it's born?
だって…。
Because…
母親だから。
I'm his mother.
とにかく僕は火影だよ。
In any case, I'm the Hokage.
簡単には死なないし→
And I'm not going to die easily.
その子は火影の俺が
何があっても守るから。 大丈夫。
And no matter what happens to me,
I, the Hokage,
will protect the child.
Don't worry!
この子のことになると
言い切るわね。
You're quite confident when
it comes to this baby!
そりゃあさ…。
Well, of course…
(父親だから))
I'm his father.
《今の俺なら…》
The current me can…
《今度こそ…》
This time for sure!
え？
What?
コイツは…。
That's—!
九尾。
Nine Tails…
これで お前を
やっと奪ってやったぞ。
You're finally mine!
どうなった？
What happened?!
ナルトは どうなんだ!?
How's Naruto?!
何なの!?
What was that?
まさか…。
No way…
マダラ様。
Lord Madara…
遅いぞ 黒ゼツ。
You're late, Black Zetsu…
こちらから出向いてやったわ。
I decided to come to you!
Madara, I need to
ask you something.
What am I to you?
You're kidding, right?
What kind of stupid question is that,
to ask at this point in time?
２時間スペシャル。
今夜のオープニングは
ご覧の豪華な歌手の皆さんと→
相模女子大学 中・高等部
合唱部の皆さんです。
曲は 高峰秀子さんの大ヒット→
皆さん ご一緒に
歌ってください。